[
  {
    "employee_number": "160301",
    "kor_name": "지은호",
    "eng_name": "Ji eunho",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "yfpxoktd@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01064856411",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 종로구 삼청로 35-1",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 종로구 삼청동 35-1",
      "zone_code": "03061",
      "detail_address": "경복궁 롯데캐슬 101동 503호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "701216",
    "rrn_back": "1356441",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "",
    "team": "",
    "position": "대표이사",
    "rank": "CEO",
    "date_of_joining": "2016년 03월 05일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "YS컴퍼니",
        "join_date": "1998년 10월 23일",
        "leave_date": "2004년 12월 03일",
        "job": "백엔드 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "대리"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "Naver",
        "join_date": "2005년 02월 06일",
        "leave_date": "2020년 07월 08일",
        "job": "백엔드 개발자",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "부장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "고등학교",
        "school_name": "서강고등학교",
        "collage": "이과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "1986년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "1989년 02월 03일"
      },
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "서강대학교",
        "collage": "컴퓨터공학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "1989년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "1997년 02월 13일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "160401",
    "kor_name": "소영미",
    "eng_name": "So yeongmi",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "hbszjlrg@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01075112658",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 중구 세종대로 110",
      "jibun_address": "서울시청 별관 1동 305호",
      "zone_code": "04524",
      "detail_address": "서울특별시 중구 태평로1가 31"
    },
    "rrn_front": "760102",
    "rrn_back": "2311258",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "영업부",
    "team": "",
    "position": "영업부장",
    "rank": "상무",
    "date_of_joining": "2016년 04월 08일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "와이에스 주식회사",
        "join_date": "2000년 03월 19일",
        "leave_date": "2002년 08월 20일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "해외영업부",
        "rank": "주임"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "진리컴퍼니",
        "join_date": "2002년 10월 18일",
        "leave_date": "2008년 10월 19일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "해외영업부",
        "rank": "과장"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "디펀트",
        "join_date": "2008년 12월 10일",
        "leave_date": "2012년 02월 03일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "해외영업부",
        "rank": "차장"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "디펀트",
        "join_date": "2013년 04월 05일",
        "leave_date": "2016년 01월 31일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "해외영업부",
        "rank": "이사"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "한국대학교",
        "collage": "경영학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "1995년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2000년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "160403",
    "kor_name": "현주희",
    "eng_name": "Hyun joohee",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "mpqwaiue@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01076205699",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 용산구 이태원로 294",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 용산구 한남동 657-1",
      "zone_code": "04350",
      "detail_address": "해밀턴호텔 1203호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "730608",
    "rrn_back": "2152017",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "프론트엔드팀",
    "position": "프론트팀장",
    "rank": "차장",
    "date_of_joining": "2016년 04월 21일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "JUST",
        "join_date": "2008년 03월 20일",
        "leave_date": "2014년 09월 17일",
        "job": "프론트 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "과장"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "JUST",
        "join_date": "2014년 09월 30일",
        "leave_date": "2016년 03월 03일",
        "job": "프론트 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "과장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "고등학교",
        "school_name": "충주고등학교",
        "collage": "문과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "1999년 03월 03일",
        "graduation_date": "2003년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "160406",
    "kor_name": "성호준",
    "eng_name": "Sung hojun",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "lnjvdcko@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01089562487",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 성동구 왕십리로 410",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 성동구 행당동 192",
      "zone_code": "04769",
      "detail_address": "센트럴자이 102동 1804호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "791025",
    "rrn_back": "1258887",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "디자인팀",
    "position": "디자인팀장",
    "rank": "차장",
    "date_of_joining": "2016년 04월 28일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "하이브",
        "join_date": "2008년 06월 12일",
        "leave_date": "2009년 03월 08일",
        "job": "웹 디자인",
        "depart": "디자인부",
        "rank": "사원"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "클리너",
        "join_date": "2009년 04월 19일",
        "leave_date": "2014년 08월 06일",
        "job": "웹 디자인",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "대리"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "클리너",
        "join_date": "2014년 08월 10일",
        "leave_date": "2016년 04월 20일",
        "job": "프론트엔드 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "대리"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "백석대학교",
        "collage": "패션디자인학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "1998년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2004년 02월 09일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "170302",
    "kor_name": "도윤석",
    "eng_name": "Do yunseok",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "xrtgqhsb@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01023586647",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 광진구 능동로 209",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 광진구 화양동 1",
      "zone_code": "05029",
      "detail_address": "건국대학교 행정관 407호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "830723",
    "rrn_back": "1388654",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "해군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "서버팀",
    "position": "서버팀장",
    "rank": "차장",
    "date_of_joining": "2017년 03월 03일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "모멘트리",
        "join_date": "2009년 05월 20일",
        "leave_date": "2012년 10월 18일",
        "job": "보안",
        "depart": "정보보안부",
        "rank": "대리"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "사이온 주식회사",
        "join_date": "2012년 12월 02일",
        "leave_date": "2016년 12월 31일",
        "job": "서버 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "과장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "한남대학교",
        "collage": "컴퓨터공학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2002년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2009년 02월 17일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "180901",
    "kor_name": "성민재",
    "eng_name": "Seong minjae",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "ezawputf@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01051235477",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 동대문구 천호대로 145",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 동대문구 회기동 14-1",
      "zone_code": "02450",
      "detail_address": "회기역 푸르지오 시티 203동 708호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "811201",
    "rrn_back": "1125445",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "",
    "position": "개발부장",
    "rank": "부장",
    "date_of_joining": "2018년 09월 14일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "넷마블",
        "join_date": "2008년 10월 10일",
        "leave_date": "2017년 12월 13일",
        "job": "프론트엔드 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "과장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "연성대학교",
        "collage": "기계공학과",
        "graduation_status": "중퇴",
        "admission_date": "2000년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2003년 08월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "181001",
    "kor_name": "지혜원",
    "eng_name": "Ji hyewon",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "bkimlcjh@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01035442377",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 중랑구 봉화산로 179",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 중랑구 신내동 647",
      "zone_code": "02121",
      "detail_address": "중랑구청 인근 래미안 105동 1102호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "850320",
    "rrn_back": "2341569",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "경영지원부",
    "team": "",
    "position": "경영지원부장",
    "rank": "부장",
    "date_of_joining": "2018년 10월 22일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "KWA산업",
        "join_date": "2003년 10월 23일",
        "leave_date": "2004년 12월 21일",
        "job": "회계",
        "depart": "경영지원부",
        "rank": "주임"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "코르코르",
        "join_date": "2005년 02월 16일",
        "leave_date": "2008년 11월 03일",
        "job": "회계",
        "depart": "재정관리부",
        "rank": "대리"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "두산중공업",
        "join_date": "2009년 02월 02일",
        "leave_date": "2015년 01월 12일",
        "job": "회계",
        "depart": "경영지원부",
        "rank": "과장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "고등학교",
        "school_name": "선화여자고등학교",
        "collage": "문과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2001년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2005년 02월 05일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "190701",
    "kor_name": "지우진",
    "eng_name": "Ji woojin",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "qsxgdnrt@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01065891173",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 성북구 동소문로 315",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 성북구 동선동1가 12",
      "zone_code": "02826",
      "detail_address": "돈암현대아파트 103동 201호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "840809",
    "rrn_back": "1169132",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "경영지원부",
    "team": "인사팀",
    "position": "인사팀장",
    "rank": "차장",
    "date_of_joining": "2019년 07월 09일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "컴투스",
        "join_date": "2010년 04월 10일",
        "leave_date": "2019년 05월 20일",
        "job": "인사",
        "depart": "경영지원부",
        "rank": "과장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "도쿄대학교",
        "collage": "경영학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2003년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2010년 02월 21일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "200302",
    "kor_name": "민서영",
    "eng_name": "Min seoyoung",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "oapvuwiy@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01038436912",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 강북구 도봉로 328",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 강북구 수유동 280",
      "zone_code": "01071",
      "detail_address": "수유동 벽산아파트 508동 1203호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "900612",
    "rrn_back": "2366571",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "경영지원부",
    "team": "회계팀",
    "position": "회계팀장",
    "rank": "과장",
    "date_of_joining": "2020년 03월 06일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "한울회계법인",
        "join_date": "2010년 02월 21일",
        "leave_date": "2012년 08월 31일",
        "job": "회계",
        "depart": "회계부",
        "rank": "주임"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "선월회계법인",
        "join_date": "2012년 09월 20일",
        "leave_date": "2014년 03월 10일",
        "job": "회계",
        "depart": "회계부",
        "rank": "대리"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "한울회계법인",
        "join_date": "2014년 04월 01일",
        "leave_date": "2013년 03월 10일",
        "job": "회계",
        "depart": "회계부",
        "rank": "차장"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "선월회계법인",
        "join_date": "2013년 09월 20일",
        "leave_date": "2019년 08월 10일",
        "job": "회계",
        "depart": "회계부",
        "rank": "차장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "고등학교",
        "school_name": "한서고등학교",
        "collage": "문과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2006년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2010년 02월 09일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "200801",
    "kor_name": "지원준",
    "eng_name": "Ji wonjun",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "jcmrhfke@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01088561247",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 도봉구 도봉로 666",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 도봉구 방학동 704",
      "zone_code": "01455",
      "detail_address": "도봉 신원아파트 108동 1702호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "920406",
    "rrn_back": "1135775",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "영업부",
    "team": "해외영업팀",
    "position": "해외영업팀장",
    "rank": "대리",
    "date_of_joining": "2020년 08월 06일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "파멕스 주식회사",
        "join_date": "2014년 09월 12일",
        "leave_date": "2020년 07월 02일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "영업부",
        "rank": "과장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "고등학교",
        "school_name": "영진고등학교",
        "collage": "자동차정비학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2008년 03월 03일",
        "graduation_date": "2012년 02월 12일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "200802",
    "kor_name": "민재윤",
    "eng_name": "Min jaeyoon",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "dtsgznbx@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01095884671",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 노원구 노해로 502",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 노원구 중계동 503",
      "zone_code": "01811",
      "detail_address": "중계동 은빛마을 201동 603호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "960912",
    "rrn_back": "1165881",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "하사"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "영업부",
    "team": "국내영업팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "대리",
    "date_of_joining": "2020년 08월 06일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "고등학교",
        "school_name": "도화기계고등학교",
        "collage": "자동차학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2012년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2016년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "200902",
    "kor_name": "현정민",
    "eng_name": "Hyun jungmin",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "fvyqiulw@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01053168412",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 은평구 은평로 195",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 은평구 구산동 4",
      "zone_code": "03306",
      "detail_address": "구산역 코오롱 하늘채 106동 1401호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "930915",
    "rrn_back": "1354842",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "영업부",
    "team": "국내영업팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "대리",
    "date_of_joining": "2020년 09월 11일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "두리화장품",
        "join_date": "2017년 06월 04일",
        "leave_date": "2020년 05월 12일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "영업부",
        "rank": "주임"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "계원예술대학교",
        "collage": "광고미디어학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2012년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2017년 02월 12일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "210501",
    "kor_name": "김지연",
    "eng_name": "Kim jiyeon",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "hkrxamjc@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01047118549",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 서대문구 통일로 360",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 서대문구 홍은동 5-1",
      "zone_code": "03740",
      "detail_address": "홍은동 래미안 루센티아 103동 302호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "960522",
    "rrn_back": "2571356",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "CEO직속",
    "team": "감사팀",
    "position": "감사팀장",
    "rank": "주임",
    "date_of_joining": "2021년 05월 10일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "한양대학교",
        "collage": "유아교육과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2015년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2020년 02월 20일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "211201",
    "kor_name": "은지윤",
    "eng_name": "Eun jieun",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "bpzsguyl@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01037112479",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 마포구 마포대로 109",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 마포구 공덕동 370",
      "zone_code": "04196",
      "detail_address": "마포한화오벨리스크 3차 2507호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "980206",
    "rrn_back": "2314613",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "경영지원부",
    "team": "인사팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "주임",
    "date_of_joining": "2021년 12월 06일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "부천대학교",
        "collage": "생활스포츠학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2017년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2019년 02월 08일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "230102",
    "kor_name": "정은주",
    "eng_name": "Jeong eunju",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "nqwtfijo@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01078115841",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 양천구 오목로 326",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 양천구 목동 409",
      "zone_code": "08089",
      "detail_address": "목동 트라팰리스 104동 803호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "970903",
    "rrn_back": "2158412",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "영업부",
    "team": "해외영업팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "대리",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 01월 05일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "메가커피",
        "join_date": "2018년 06월 10일",
        "leave_date": "2022년 10월 11일",
        "job": "마케팅",
        "depart": "마케팅부",
        "rank": "주임"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "재능대학교",
        "collage": "디지털바이오테크학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2016년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2018년 02월 13일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "230201",
    "kor_name": "이승민",
    "eng_name": "Lee seungmin",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "ckshvaex@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01034088801",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 강서구 강서로 388",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 강서구 등촌동 647-2",
      "zone_code": "07647",
      "detail_address": "등촌 자이아파트 207동 1601호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "970513",
    "rrn_back": "1611357",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "해군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "CEO직속",
    "team": "감사팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "주임",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 02월 06일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "Audi Korea",
        "join_date": "2023년 03월 07일",
        "leave_date": "2023년 11월 28일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "영업부",
        "rank": "대리"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "호서대학교",
        "collage": "기계공학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2016년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2022년 02월 13일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "230501",
    "kor_name": "강준호",
    "eng_name": "Kang junho",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "jpugybfq@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01075133518",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 구로구 디지털로 306",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 구로구 구로동 642",
      "zone_code": "08378",
      "detail_address": "구로 푸르지오 102동 1105호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "950613",
    "rrn_back": "1511548",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "하사"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "영업부",
    "team": "해외영업팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "사원",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 05월 07일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "강원대학교",
        "collage": "소방학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2018년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2023년 02월 16일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "230502",
    "kor_name": "윤서현",
    "eng_name": "Yoon seohyun",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "wrtzlxdh@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01042158865",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 금천구 시흥대로 399",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 금천구 독산동 291",
      "zone_code": "08608",
      "detail_address": "독산동 위브 센트럴파크 1603호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "960815",
    "rrn_back": "2812335",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "프론트엔드팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "주임",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 05월 07일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "하이트진로",
        "join_date": "2020년 08월 28일",
        "leave_date": "2023년 01월 12일",
        "job": "프론트엔드 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "주임"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "한양대학교",
        "collage": "컴퓨터공학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2015년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2020년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "230601",
    "kor_name": "박민준",
    "eng_name": "Park minjun",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "mvsiakgc@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01058135645",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 영등포구 국제금융로 52",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 영등포구 여의도동 23",
      "zone_code": "07329",
      "detail_address": "여의도 리버뷰 트윈 1002호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "000715",
    "rrn_back": "3152617",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "경영지원부",
    "team": "인사팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "주임",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 06월 12일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "영남대학교",
        "collage": "경제학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2019년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2023년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "230602",
    "kor_name": "최지원",
    "eng_name": "Choi jiwon",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "epxuqhrt@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01037822614",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 동작구 노량진로 148",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 동작구 노량진동 332",
      "zone_code": "06939",
      "detail_address": "노량진 한강로얄파크 1005호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "970531",
    "rrn_back": "2416912",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "경영지원부",
    "team": "회계팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "주임",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 06월 15일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "바이오다인",
        "join_date": "2020년 06월 12일",
        "leave_date": "2023년 04월 10일",
        "job": "회계",
        "depart": "회계부",
        "rank": "주임"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "부산대학교",
        "collage": "회계학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2016년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2020년 02월 13일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "230901",
    "kor_name": "장민석",
    "eng_name": "Jang minseok",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "gybjhzfx@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01064775283",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 관악구 남부순환로 1820",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 관악구 신림동 1430-7",
      "zone_code": "08788",
      "detail_address": "신림동 래미안 블레스티지 302동 1208호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "970811",
    "rrn_back": "1162845",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "공군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "디자인팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "주임",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 09월 17일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "아메코젠 주식회사",
        "join_date": "2020년 04월 08일",
        "leave_date": "2023년 08월 10일",
        "job": "웹 디자인",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "주임"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "인하대학교",
        "collage": "스마트디지털엔지니어링과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2016년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2020년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "230902",
    "kor_name": "오지현",
    "eng_name": "Oh jihyun",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "ufqkltwa@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01055129984",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 서초구 강남대로 369",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 서초구 서초동 1305-3",
      "zone_code": "06611",
      "detail_address": "서초동 하이브랜드 501호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "000430",
    "rrn_back": "4129983",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "서버팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "사원",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 09월 17일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "인하대학교",
        "collage": "미디어커뮤니케이션학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2019년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2023년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "231001",
    "kor_name": "선우현",
    "eng_name": "Sun woohyun",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "nrpojcvi@example.com",
    "phone_number": "0106891546",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 강남구 도산대로 514",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 강남구 청담동 95-15",
      "zone_code": "06015",
      "detail_address": "청담 에스티마 103동 3004호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "951202",
    "rrn_back": "1689443",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "경영지원부",
    "team": "정보보안팀",
    "position": "정보보안팀장",
    "rank": "대리",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 10월 02일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "동원테크",
        "join_date": "2021년 03월 03일",
        "leave_date": "2023년 06월 10일",
        "job": "정보보안",
        "depart": "보안팀",
        "rank": "주임"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "구미대학교",
        "collage": "정보보안학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2014년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2021년 02월 04일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "231002",
    "kor_name": "황성우",
    "eng_name": "Hwang sungwoo",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "xthaywsq@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01065843251",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 송파구 백제고분로 426",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 송파구 신천동 7",
      "zone_code": "05699",
      "detail_address": "송파파크 데일 103동 2702호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "980209",
    "rrn_back": "1168235",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "공군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "프론트엔드팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "사원",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 10월 02일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "고등학교",
        "school_name": "서울과학고등학교",
        "collage": "",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2014년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2017년 02월 10일"
      },
      {
        "school_classification": "고려대학교",
        "school_name": "서울과학고등학교",
        "collage": "컴퓨터과학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2017년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2023년 02월 06일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "231003",
    "kor_name": "지민우",
    "eng_name": "Ji minwoo",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "iklhzfbo@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01039495594",
    "address": {
      "address": "서울특별시 강동구 천호대로 1017",
      "jibun_address": "서울특별시 강동구 성내동 434",
      "zone_code": "05359",
      "detail_address": "강동구청역 롯데캐슬 502동 804호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "950716",
    "rrn_back": "1656135",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "프론트엔드팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "대리",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 10월 02일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "영실업",
        "join_date": "2018년 05월 29일",
        "leave_date": "2023년 07월 10일",
        "job": "프론트엔드 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "대리"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "한국대학교",
        "collage": "전기공학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2014년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2018년 02월 05일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "231004",
    "kor_name": "현우진",
    "eng_name": "Hyun woojin",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "aqjgxdsc@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01045664358",
    "address": {
      "address": "인천광역시 중구 차이나타운로 59",
      "jibun_address": "인천광역시 중구 북성동1가 97-1",
      "zone_code": "22332",
      "detail_address": "개항장 현대아파트 102동 1103호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "900612",
    "rrn_back": "1569474",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "영업부",
    "team": "국내영업팀",
    "position": "국내영업팀장",
    "rank": "이사",
    "date_of_joining": "2023년 10월 02일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "카카오",
        "join_date": "2013년 07월 02일",
        "leave_date": "2023년 01월 06일",
        "job": "프론트엔드 개발",
        "depart": "개발부",
        "rank": "과장"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "졸업",
        "school_name": "경희대학교",
        "collage": "컴퓨터공학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2009년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2013년 02월 13일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "240101",
    "kor_name": "서연우",
    "eng_name": "Seo yeonwoo",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "rvfunezt@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01096849743",
    "address": {
      "address": "인천광역시 동구 화도진로 155",
      "jibun_address": "인천광역시 동구 송림동 77",
      "zone_code": "22573",
      "detail_address": "송림동 풍림아이원 1204동 901호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "960823",
    "rrn_back": "1694331",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "영업부",
    "team": "국내영업팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "대리",
    "date_of_joining": "2024년 01월 06일",
    "career": [
      {
        "company_name": "한샘인테리어",
        "join_date": "2015년 08월 10일",
        "leave_date": "2018년 10월 02일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "영업부",
        "rank": "주임"
      },
      {
        "company_name": "KT",
        "join_date": "2019년 01월 02일",
        "leave_date": "2023년 09월 14일",
        "job": "영업",
        "depart": "영업부",
        "rank": "대리"
      }
    ],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "고등학교",
        "school_name": "한서고등학교",
        "collage": "이과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2012년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2015년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "240102",
    "kor_name": "신지호",
    "eng_name": "Shin jiho",
    "sex": "남성",
    "email": "pwsoibjh@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01026884641",
    "address": {
      "address": "인천광역시 미추홀구 인하로 497-24",
      "jibun_address": "인천광역시 미추홀구 주안동 873",
      "zone_code": "22146",
      "detail_address": "주안 현대 3차 1002동 203호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "970521",
    "rrn_back": "1694457",
    "military": {
      "division": "군필",
      "army": "육군",
      "rank": "병장"
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "프론트엔드팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "사원",
    "date_of_joining": "2024년 01월 06일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "동명대학교",
        "collage": "컴퓨터공학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2017년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2023년 02월 10일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "240201",
    "kor_name": "박지원",
    "eng_name": "Park jiwon",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "tmlqgzck@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01061334613",
    "address": {
      "address": "인천광역시 연수구 청학동 423",
      "jibun_address": "인천광역시 연수구 청학동 145-5",
      "zone_code": "21988",
      "detail_address": "송도 센트럴파크 푸르지오 204동 2701호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "030103",
    "rrn_back": "4162325",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "디자인팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "사원",
    "date_of_joining": "2024년 02월 08일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "신안산대학교",
        "collage": "디자인과",
        "graduation_status": "",
        "admission_date": "2022년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2024년 02월 07일"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "employee_number": "240202",
    "kor_name": "정승연",
    "eng_name": "Jeong seungyeon",
    "sex": "여성",
    "email": "hbxwfsev@example.com",
    "phone_number": "01049669774",
    "address": {
      "address": "인천광역시 남동구 논현대로 760",
      "jibun_address": "인천광역시 남동구 논현동 618",
      "zone_code": "21697",
      "detail_address": "논현동 두산위브더제니스 103동 1605호"
    },
    "rrn_front": "000623",
    "rrn_back": "4661915",
    "military": {
      "division": "미필",
      "army": "",
      "rank": ""
    },
    "quarter": "본사",
    "department": "개발부",
    "team": "서버팀",
    "position": "",
    "rank": "사원",
    "date_of_joining": "2024년 02월 21일",
    "career": [],
    "edu": [
      {
        "school_classification": "대학교",
        "school_name": "명지대학교",
        "collage": "컴퓨터공학과",
        "graduation_status": "졸업",
        "admission_date": "2020년 03월 02일",
        "graduation_date": "2024년 02월 12일"
      }
    ]
  }
]